Guide to the Institute on the Arts and Civic Dialogue Archive 1997-2000 MSS 127 MSS 127
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 4: Video Recordings
  - Subseries 4.1: Video Recordings Access Copies
    - Brandon, Tapes #A1-A5, undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 127.0022)
      Video recording, VHS, Maxell T-160 std, SP, RT: 2:30:00
    - House Arrest, Tapes #1A-5A, IACD workshop production, undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 127.0024)
      Video recording, VHS, Maxell T-160 Pro, SP, RT: 2:35:00
    - Anna Deavere Smith, House Arrest, Act I. New York Production, 2000 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 127.0026)
      Video recording, VHS, Maxell T-90 std, SP, RT: 1:12:11, Recorded 4/13/2000
    - Anna Deavere Smith, House Arrest, Act II. New York Production, 2000 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 127.0028)
      Video recording, VHS, Maxell T-90 std, SP, RT: 59:59, Recorded 4/13/2000
    - Common Infractions: Gross Injustices, Tape #1B, undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 127.003)
      Video recording, VHS, Maxell T-30 std, SP, RT: 28:00
    - The Minstrel Show, Tapes #1,2, undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 127.0032)
      Video recording, VHS, Maxell T-60 std, SP, RT: 53:00
    - The Minstrel Show, Tapes #3,4, undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 127.0034)
      Video recording, VHS, Maxell T-90 std, SP, RT: 1:00:00
    - Massachusetts Foundation for the Humanities, Stories to Be Told; The Unfound Door; Chautauqua Institution, undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 127.0036)
      Video recording, VHS, Maxell T-60 std, SP, RTs: 10:40, 7:50, 21:10
  - Subseries 4.2: Video Recordings Archival Copies
    Archival copies of the video recordings, not to be viewed. Arranged as received.
    - Institute on the Arts and Civic Dialogue, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 127.0007)
    - Institute on the Arts and Civic Dialogue, Off-Line Edit, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 127.0009)
    - Anna Deavere Smith With Bill Barbeaux, Summer 1999 (Box 14, Folder 127.0011)
    - Musical Prayers, Summer 2000, Tape 1 (Box 14, Folder 127.0013)
    - Musical Prayers, Summer 2000, Tape 2 (Box 14, Folder 127.0015)
    - Public Art, Public Land by Judy Baca, Tapes #1-3, undated (Box 14, Folder 127.0017)
    - High Noon, Tapes #1, 3, 5, 7, 9, undated (Box 14, Folder 127.0019)
    - Brandon, Tapes #1, 3, 5, 7, 9, undated (Box 14, Folder 127.0021)
    - Brandon, Tapes #A1-A5, undated (Box 14, Folder 127.0023)
    - House Arrest, Tapes #1A-5A, IACD workshop production, undated (Box 14, Folder 127.0025)
    - Anna Deavere Smith, House Arrest, Act I. New York Production, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 127.0027)
    - Anna Deavere Smith, House Arrest, Act II. New York Production, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 127.0029)
    - Common Infractions: Gross Injustices, Tape #1B, undated (Box 14, Folder 127.0031)
    - The Minstrel Show, Tapes #1,2, undated (Box 14, Folder 127.0033)
    - The Minstrel Show, Tapes #3,4, undated (Box 14, Folder 127.0035)
    - Massachusetts Foundation for the Humanities, Stories to Be Told; The Unfound Door; Chautauqua Institution, undated (Box 14, Folder 127.0037)